parentteacheronline.com.au 2019-06-20

# Privacy Policy - Parent Teacher Online

Country Net Software Pty Ltd, owners of Parent Teacher Online provide the following Privacy Statement

**SERVER AND DATA LOCATION**  
**We own all our own servers and do not rely on third party hosted solutions. Our servers are co-located  ** **at: Macquarie Datacentre 17-23 Talavera Rd, Macquarie Park NSW 2113.**  
Our structure meets all privacy policy at federal and individual state and territory levels in Australia with 128 bit encryption at industry standards.

**COLLECTING ANONYMOUS INFORMATION**  
We automatically collect general website traffic information (such as how many people have visited the site, most popular pages etc). This information is collected into aggregate results in order to evaluate our service and business practice.

We may share non-personal, aggregated information while demonstrating to other schools or for research purposes. We will never identify or disclose individual customers or visitors information, but may disclose how many users and traffic volumes to other potential schools.

**COLLECTING PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
We collect personal information submitted by schools or parents to manage and deliver the parent teacher interview booking service. We do not disclose personal information to any person/s or organisations for any purpose.

**USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
We will use personal information as supplied by schools or parents to process and deliver our service. We do not disclose any information unless information is accessed via a login and password. We also retain archived information in a secure online system that is available by schools for future use. This is so we have a record of all transactions should a school wish to retrieve such information.

We do not publish personal information about an individual or a school.

Under no circumstances will Country Net Software Pty Ltd (Owners of PTO) sell or receive payment for licensing or disclosing your personal information.

**COOKIES**  
We DO NOT use cookies.

**PRIVACY**  
Personal information like address, phone etc is not collected to deliver our PTO service. Once you have logged in your account will remain open until you quit the browser or you log out, or there is a time out, whichever occurs first.

**EMAIL ADDRESSES**  
In the event that you or your school provides us with your email address, we will store your email address if you: send us a query; place an order or subscribe to information. Your email address is used for the purpose you provide it for and for statistical information. We will from time to time send emails to registered administrator accounts with details of system updates. Administrators may opt out of these communications using instructions provided in the message.

Email addresses are never used or disclosed for any other purpose.

**SPAM**  
We will never knowingly send you electronic messages without your consent. For more information on the ‘Spam Act 2003′ please visit the Australian Government’s relevant website.

**FIREWALL**  
Our system is protected by the Country Net Software network firewall. A firewall is a hardware and software security system designed to filter specified exchanges of information and restrict access to authorised systems and users.

**THIRD PARTIES**  
Country Net Software never sells personal or anonymous information to third parties.

**AUSTRALIAN LAW**  
We comply with the Trade Practices Act 1974, state based Fair Trading Acts and Sale of Goods Acts, the Consumer Credit Code, the Electronic Transactions Act 1999 the Information Privacy Principles set out in the Commonwealth Privacy Act 1988; and the Privacy Amendment (Private Sector) Act 2000 (Cth).

Dispute resolution services are available in each Australian State and Territory.

**FEEDBACK AND COMPLAINTS HANDLING PROCEDURE**  
Country Net Software welcomes feedback and attends to all complaints promptly. Please email, fax or write to us using the contact information provided on our website.
